Finding Aid for the Anthony C. Beilenson Papers LSC.0391
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Legislation
  - Bills / subject
    - Legal immigration op ed (Box 405, Folder 1)
      Research material, manuscript drafts. Includes: Statement of Congressman Anthony C. Beilenson against the Chrysler / Berman / Brownback amendment to HR 2202 striking legal immigration provisions. 1996 Mar 21. 3 l. Typescript (printer). Also: It's time to address immigration and its effect on U.S. population growth by Rep. Anthony C. Beilenson. No date. 4 l. Typescript (printer). Also earlier versions of this text. Also cover letters to various newspaper editors enclosing this manuscript. Also: Missing from the campaign: immigration and its effect on U.S. population growth by Rep. Anthony C. Beilenson. 4 l. Typescript
    - Population commission (Box 405, Folder 2)
      Copy of bill, not introduced, clippings. Also: Statement of Congressman Anthony C. Beilenson before the Subcommittee on foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, of the House Committee on Appropriations. 1996 Apr 25. 11 l. Typescript (large font, printer). Also: Population growth is the great enemy [clipping from] The Los Angeles Times. 1990 Jul 23 (Monday). Also: Politics and Society: Political Challenges of Confronting Population Growth by Congressman Anthony C. Beilenson. 1992. 24 l. Typescript (printer)
    - Budget (Box 405, Folder 3)
      [Not in folder] Clippings, statements. Includes: Remarks of Congressman Anthony C. Beilenson on President Bush's FY 1992 budget. 1991 Feb 6. [2] l. Typescript (printer). Also: Dissenting views of Rep. Anthony C. Beilenson [on budget]. No date. [2] l. Typescript (printer)
    - Bill drafting (Box 405, Folder 4)
      ACB's notes
    - Franked mail out of district (Box 405, Folder 5)
      Clipping, letter to editor. Includes: Congressman Beilenson calls for end of congressional mail abuse / pledges not to use franking loophole. 1992 Jan 22
    - One - minute letter final draft (Box 405, Folder 6)
      CRS report, research material. Cf. material in Box ___ f. ___
    - Pay raise bill. f.1 of 2 (Box 405, Folder 7)
      CRS report, draft press release, etc
    - Pay raise bill. f.2 of 2 (Box 405, Folder 8)
    - Line item veto. f.1 of 2 (Box 405, Folder 9)
      Research material, analysis, copies of legislation, clippings, etc
    - Line item veto. f.2 of 2 (Box 405, Folder 10)
    - Crime bill (Box 405, Folder 11)
      Copies of bill, amendment offered to HR 4092 by ACB
  - Committees
    - Research
      - Population - United Nations and European studies, reports. (Box 248, Folder 2)
        Also ACB's notes
    - Select Committee on Population
      - Population - legislation and research file (Box 248, Folder 1)
        Notes, bills, etc
  - Congressional Record
    - Inserts
      - For the date noted (Box 437)
      - For the date noted (Box 437)
      - For the date noted (Box 437)
      - For the date noted (Box 437)
      - For the date noted (Box 437)
      - For the date noted (Box 437)
      - For the date noted (Box 437)
      - For the date noted (Box 437)
      - For the date noted (Box 437)
      - For the date noted (Box 437)
      - For the date noted (Box 437)
      - For the date noted (Box 437)
      - For the date noted (Box 438)
      - For the date noted (Box 438)
      - For the date noted (Box 438)
      - For the date noted (Box 438)
      - For the date noted (Box 438)
      - For the date noted (Box 438)
      - For the date noted (Box 438)
      - For the date noted (Box 438)
  - Legislation
    - Introduced
      - HR 2202 (Box 328, Folder 11)
        Status sheet for Immigration in the National Interest Act of 1995
      - H.J. Res. 117 (Citizenship Constitutional amendment) (Box 328, Folder 12)
        Joint resolution, status sheet, summary of legislation
      - H.J. Res. 56 (Citizenship Amendment) (Box 328, Folder 13)
        Dear colleague letter, News report: Congressman Beilenson calls for Denying U.S. Citizenship to Children of Illegal Immigrants, status sheet, Press release: Congressman Beilenson Calls for Support of His Constitutional Amendment to Deny Automatic Citizenship to U.S. Born Children of Illegal Immigrants. Also: Statement of Congressman Anthony C. Beilenson before the Subcommittee on Immigration and Claims House Committee on the Judiciary. 1995 Dec 13. 6 l. Typescript (photocopy)
    - Voting records
      - For the dates noted (Box 459)
  - Legislative activity
    - 100th Congress first session
      - For the dates noted. f.1 of 3 (Box 455)
      - For the dates noted. f.3 of 3 (Box 455)
      - For the dates noted. f.2 of 3 (Box 455)
      - For the dates noted (Box 462)
    - 100th Congress second session
      - For the dates noted. f.3 of 3 (Box 455)
      - For the dates noted. f.2 of 2 (Box 455)
      - For the dates noted. f.1 of 3 (Box 455)
      - For the dates noted (Box 462)
    - 101st Congress first session
      - For the dates noted. f.2 of 2 (Box 456)
      - For the dates noted. f.1 of 2 (Box 456)
      - For the dates noted (Box 463)
    - 101st Congress second session
      - For the dates noted. f.1 of 3 (Box 456)
      - For the dates noted. f.2 of 3 (Box 456)
      - For the dates noted. f.3 of 3 (Box 456)
      - For the dates noted (Box 463)
    - 102nd Congress first session
      - For the dates noted. f.2 of 2 (Box 457)
      - For the dates noted. f.1 of 3 (Box 457)
      - For the dates noted (Box 463)
    - 102nd Congress second session
      - For the dates noted. F.2 of 1 (Box 457)
      - For the dates noted. F.1 of 2 (Box 457)
    - 103rd Congress first session
      - For the dates noted (Box 458)
    - 103rd Congress second session
      - For the dates noted (Box 458)
    - 104th Congress first session
      - For the dates noted. F.1 of 2 (Box 458)
      - For the dates noted. F.2 of 2 (Box 458)
    - 104th Congress second session
      - For the dates noted. F.1 of 2 (Box 458)
      - For the dates noted. F.2 of 2 (Box 458)
    - 95th Congress first session
      - For the dates noted (Box 459)
    - 95th Congress second session
      - For the dates noted (Box 459)
    - 96th Congress first session
      - For the dates noted (Box 460)
    - 96th Congress second session
      - For the dates noted (Box 460)
        [97th Congress filed later boxes, because of size]
    - 97th Congress first session
      - For the dates noted (Box 464)
    - 97th Congress second session
      - For the dates noted (Box 464)
    - 98th Congress first session
      - For the dates noted (Box 461)
    - 98th Congress second session
      - For the dates noted (Box 461)
    - 99th Congress first sessions
      - For the dates noted (Box 461)
    - 99th Congress second session
      - For the dates noted (Box 462)
    - ACB's votes
      - Interesting votes list (Box 464)
        Beilenson interesting votes (updated 5/93)
  - Legislative activity guide
    - 99th Congress first session
      - For the dates noted. f.1 of 2 (Box 452)
      - For the dates noted. f.2 of 2 (Box 452)
    - 99th Congress second session
      - For the dates noted. f.1 of 2 (Box 452)
      - For the dates noted. f.2 of 2 (Box 452)
  - Office management
    - Interns
      - Notebook [job manual] (Box 437)
        Also Congressional manual
  - Research
    - Billboards (Box 239, Folder 10)
    - Beilenson [so labeled] (Box 239, Folder 11)
      Issues of interest to ACB, including highway issues. Includes transcript of a Rules Committee debate, 1991 Dec 9.
    - Transportation bills and analysis (Box 239, Folder 12)
    - Highway construction warranties (Box 239, Folder 13)
      Memos, press release: Beilenson contract guarantee amendment for highway work is approved by House of Representatives, 1991 Oct 23. Also includes further copies of Rules Committee debate, 1991 Dec 9, filed previously
    - Contractor warranty / guarantee Dear Colleague letter (Box 239, Folder 14)
      Save taxpayers billions of collars: let states demand guarantees from highway contractors
    - Abortion. f.1 of 2 (Box 248, Folder 3)
      ACB's notes, statements, reports, clippings. In response to renewed "pro-life" legislation. These research files contain earlier materials, evidently brought together from ACB's state legislative positions
    - Abortion. f.2 of 2 (Box 248, Folder 4)
    - Abortion. f.1 of 2 (Box 248, Folder 5)
      Notes, reports, clippings
    - Abortion. f.2 of 2 (Box 248, Folder 6)
    - Sterilization. f.1 of 2 (Box 248, Folder 7)
    - Sterilization. f.2 of 2 (Box 248, Folder 8)
    - Abortion. f.1 of 2 (Box 249, Folder 1)
      Notes, reports, statements
    - Abortion. f.2 of 2 (Box 249, Folder 2)
    - Family planning (Box 249, Folder 3)
    - Population. f.1 of 2 (Box 249, Folder 4)
      ACB's notes, reports, clippings
    - Population. f.2 of 2 (Box 249, Folder 5)
    - Global population. f.1 of 3 (Box 250, Folder 1)
    - Global population. f.2 of 3 (Box 250, Folder 2)
    - Global population. f.3 of 3 (Box 250, Folder 3)
    - Birth control and contraceptives - teenagers (Box 250, Folder 4)
    - Population. f.1 of 2 (Box 250, Folder 5)
    - Population. f.2 of 2 (Box 250, Folder 6)
    - Population. f.1 of 5 (Box 251, Folder 1)
      Reports. All this box were unfoldered
    - Population. f.2 of 5 (Box 251, Folder 2)
    - Population. f.3 of 5 (Box 251, Folder 3)
    - Population. f.4 of 5 (Box 251, Folder 4)
    - Population. f.5 of 5 (Box 251, Folder 5)
      Family Planning Perspectives, various issues 1969, 1970, 1972
    - Family planning. f.1 of 5 (Box 252, Folder 1)
    - Family planning. f.2 of 5 (Box 252, Folder 2)
    - Family planning. f.3 of 5 (Box 252, Folder 3)
    - Family planning. f.4 of 5 (Box 252, Folder 4)
    - Family planning. f.5 of 5 (Box 252, Folder 5)
    - Teenage pregnancy. f.1 of 2 (Box 253, Folder 1)
    - Teenage pregnancy. f.2 of 2 (Box 253, Folder 2)
    - Population. f.1 of 2 (Box 253, Folder 3)
    - Population. f.2 of 2 (Box 253, Folder 4)
    - Population. f.1 of 2 (Box 253, Folder 5)
    - Population. f.2 of 2 (Box 253, Folder 6)
    - Population (planned parenthood) (Box 253, Folder 7)
      Includes report, IPPF and its future, 1977 Sep
    - Reproductive freedom (Box 254, Folder 1)
      Reproductive Freedom: A Human Right --- Government's Responsibility. Remarks by ACB at the annual meeting of Planned Parenthood Federation of America, 1978 Oct 25, San Diego CA. Typescript (mimeograph or photocopy) 22 l
    - [ACB's] Abortion act (Box 254, Folder 2)
      Jain, Sagar C., and Steven Hughes with the assistance of Marilyn Carlson. California Abortion Act 1967: A Study in Legislation. Carolina Population Center, University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill, 1969
    - Population. f.1 of 6 (Box 254, Folder 3)
    - Population. f.2 of 6 (Box 254, Folder 4)
    - Population. f.3 of 6 (Box 254, Folder 5)
    - Population. f.4 of 6 (Box 254, Folder 6)
    - Population. f.5 of 6 (Box 254, Folder 7)
    - Population. f.6 of 6 (Box 254, Folder 8)
    - Population. f.1 of 3 (Box 255, Folder 1)
    - Population. f.2 of 3 (Box 255, Folder 2)
    - Population. f.3 of 3 (Box 255, Folder 3)
    - House Select Committee on Population (Box 255, Folder 4)
    - House Select Committee on Hunger (Box 255, Folder 5)
    - Population (Box 255, Folder 6)
    - Guatemala (Box 257, Folder 1)
    - Bosnia - Herzegovina (Box 257, Folder 2)
      Reports, clippings (photocopies). Includes Act Now to End This Holocaust (by ACB) 4 l. Typescript (printer copy). With letter from ACB to Editorial Page Editor, The Washington Post 1992 Dec 2
    - Golan Heights (Box 257, Folder 3)
      One flier
    - Israel / Jewish groups. f.1 of 2 (Box 257, Folder 4)
      Memos, statements. Includes lists of ACB's support of legislation regarding Jewish or Israeli concerns
    - Israel / Jewish groups. f.2 of 2 (Box 257, Folder 5)
    - Haiti (Box 257, Folder 6)
    - Pakistan / Kashmir (Box 257, Folder 7)
      Position letter (not by ACB)
    - Nicaragua (Box 257, Folder 8)
      Resolution, clippings (not an extensive file)
    - Panama (Box 257, Folder 9)
      CRS Issue briefs, clippings, etc
    - Chile (Box 257, Folder 10)
      CRS report for Congress
    - Peru (Box 257, Folder 11)
      Congressional statements, clippings
    - Europe (Box 257, Folder 12)
      Clippings, CRS issue brief, etc
    - Sub - Saharan Africa (Box 257, Folder 13)
      Congressional reports, clipping
    - South Africa (Box 257, Folder 14)
      CRS report, African National Congress leadership chart
    - Eastern Europe (except Germany) (Box 257, Folder 15)
      CRS review, reports
    - Lithuania letter (Box 257, Folder 16)
      Copy of letter signed by ACB and others, regarding further investigation of WW II crimes by Lithuanians and not blanket exoneration from Soviet tribunals
    - Ethiopian Jewry (Box 257, Folder 17)
      Clippings, CRS issue brief
    - Syrian Jews (Box 257, Folder 18)
      Fact sheets, news releases
    - Lebanon (Box 257, Folder 19)
      One letter received
    - Germany (Box 257, Folder 20)
      One memo from GES (ACB staff?)
    - Hungary / Romania (Box 257, Folder 21)
      Memos with enclosures, clippings
    - Iran (Box 257, Folder 22)
      Background information on support of various factions in Iran and requests for congressional supporters. An extensive file
    - Jordan (Box 257, Folder 23)
      Jordan and Palestinian refugees, includes CIA chart of Palestinian leaderships
    - Yugoslavia (Box 257, Folder 24)
      CRS report, issue brief, other reports
    - Japan (Box 257, Folder 25)
      Memos, charts
    - Burma (Box 257, Folder 26)
      Congressional letters, background
    - Indonesia / East Timor (Box 258, Folder 1)
    - Cambodia (Box 258, Folder 2)
      CRS report, issue brief, draft statements, clippings
    - Kuwait (Box 258, Folder 3)
      Dept of Commerce report
    - Iraq (Box 258, Folder 4)
      Senator Al Gore address
    - Mexican loan guarantees (Box 258, Folder 5)
      Memos, staff summaries
    - Afghanistan (Box 258, Folder 6)
      Reprint of ACB's New York Times article, End Aid to the Afghan Rebels (1898 May 22), background reports
    - Vietnam. f.1 of 2 (Box 258, Folder 7)
      CRS issue brief, notes
    - Vietnam. f.2 of 2 (Box 258, Folder 8)
    - China. f.1 of 2 (Box 258, Folder 9)
      Letters from President Bill Clinton. 1993 Jun 29. 1 l. Typed, signed. 1993 Jun 30. 1 l. Typed, signed. Letter Jun 29 is actually about missile defense
    - China. f.2 of 2 (Box 258, Folder 10)
      Reports, CIA chart of Chinese Communist Party Central Committee
    - Commission on Security and Cooperation in Europe / Helsinki (Box 258, Folder 11)
      Reports, copy of The Helskini Final Act
    - U.N. Conference on Environment and Development (Box 258, Folder 12)
    - Conventional Armed Forces in Europe (Box 258, Folder 13)
      Memos, copies of treaty
    - United Nations / treaties (Box 258, Folder 14)
    - Free trade agreements (Box 258, Folder 15)
      DSG reports, clippings
    - International trade (Box 258, Folder 16)
      Reports, from CRS and the White House
    - Foreign policy op ed (Box 258, Folder 17)
      Position statements, texts. Includes: A Broader View of the U.S. National Interests: New Directions for U.S. Foreign Policy, an address by Congressman Anthony C. Beilenson, January 26, 1989, Los Angeles World Affairs Council. 14 p. Typescript (printer)
    - Soviet republics. F.1 of 2 (Box 258, Folder 18)
      Letter from President George Bush. 1992 Aug 3. 3 l. Typed, signed
    - Soviet republics. F.2 of 2 (Box 258, Folder 19)
      Letter from Secretary of State James Baker with enclosure, CRS reports, issue briefs, DSG reports
    - Voice of America transmitter in Israel (Box 259, Folder 1)
      Reports, position statements for and against the transmitter. An extensive file
    - International criminal court (Box 259, Folder 2)
      Fact sheets, reports
    - International economics (Box 259, Folder 3)
      Memo on foreign investment
    - Democracy (Box 259, Folder 4)
      Extending freedoms throughout the world. Op ed statements, clippings
    - International Conference on Population and Development (Box 259, Folder 5)
      Organizing statements
    - Armenia (Box 259, Folder 6)
      Memos, reports. An extensive file
    - Arab boycott joint letter (Box 259, Folder 7)
      Memos, reports, clippings. Includes: Statement by Hon. Anthony Beilenson Regarding his 5 / 24 / 91 letter to commerce Secretary Mosbacher on Ending the Arab Boycott of Israel .... 3 l. Typescript (printer)
    - Arctic islands (Box 259, Folder 8)
      Memos, fact sheets
    - Boznia - Herzegovina. f.1 of 2 (Box 259, Folder 9)
    - Boznia - Herzegovina. f.2 of 2 (Box 259, Folder 10)
    - Central America (Box 259, Folder 11)
      Two fact sheets
    - El Salvador (Box 259, Folder 12)
    - International Conference on Population and Development (Box 260, Folder 1)
      Cairo conference prospectus
    - International family planning letter (Box 260, Folder 2)
      To House Subcommittee on Foreign Operations. Beilenson a signator
    - World Population Awareness Week (Box 260, Folder 3)
      Letter to ACB, House resolution, etc
    - Population: environmental - general (Box 260, Folder 4)
      Reports, articles
    - Population: a finite world - limited resources (Box 260, Folder 5)
      Speech by Russell Petersen, clippings
    - Population: a finite world - food resources (Box 260, Folder 6)
    - Population: poverty (Box 260, Folder 7)
      Internal memo, clippings
    - Population: migration (Box 260, Folder 8)
    - Population: cities. f.1 of 2 (Box 261, Folder 1)
    - Population: cities. f.2 of 2 (Box 261, Folder 2)
    - Population: optimum size (Box 261, Folder 3)
    - Population: views opposing control. f.1 of 2 (Box 261, Folder 4)
    - Population: views opposing control. f.2 of 2 (Box 261, Folder 5)
    - Population: ominous demographics (Box 261, Folder 6)
    - Population: environmental - air (Box 261, Folder 7)
    - Population: not enough jobs (Box 261, Folder 8)
      Two clippings
    - Population: development. f.1 of 2 (Box 261, Folder 9)
    - Population: development. f.2 of 2 (Box 261, Folder 10)
    - RU - 486. f.1 of 2 (Box 261, Folder 11)
    - RU - 486. f.2 of 2 (Box 261, Folder 12)
    - Norplant. f.1 of 2 (Box 261, Folder 13)
    - Norplant. f.2 of 2 (Box 261, Folder 14)
    - Population: Depo - Provera (Box 261, Folder 15)
    - Family planning: condom use (Box 261, Folder 16)
    - Family planning: contraceptives (Box 261, Folder 17)
    - Population: USA / California (Box 261, Folder 18)
    - Family planning: ACB statement. f.1 of 9 (Box 262, Folder 1)
      Statement of Rep. Anthony C. Beilenson before the House committee on Interstate and Foreign Commerce - Subcommittee on Health and the Environment. 1978 Feb 21. 5 l. Typescript (photocopy)
    - Family planning: ACB statement. f.2 of 9 (Box 262, Folder 2)
      Statement presented to the National Family Planning Forum. 1978 Mar. 17 l. Typescript (photocopy)
    - Family planning: ACB statement. f.3 of 9 (Box 262, Folder 3)
      Extension of remarks. 5 l. Typescript (photocopy)
    - Family planning: ACB statement. f.4 of 9 (Box 262, Folder 4)
      Remarks prepared for Rep. Anthony C. Beilenson, Planned Parenthood Federation of America annual meeting, San Diego, California. 1978 Oct 23. t.p., 5 l. Typescript (large type, photocopy)
    - Family planning: ACB statement. f.5 of 9 (Box 262, Folder 5)
      Statement of Rep. Anthony C. Beilenson at the press conference of the House Select Committee on Population on its report, "Fertility and Contraception in the United States." 1979 Apr 24. 5 l. Typescript (photocopy)
    - Family planning: ACB statement. f.6 of 9 (Box 262, Folder 6)
      Statement of Representative Anthony C. Beilenson before the House Committee on Appropriations - Subcommittee on Labor, Health, Education and Welfare. 1979 Apr 26. 7 l. Typescript (photocopy)
    - Family planning: ACB statement. f.7 of 9 (Box 262, Folder 7)
      Statement of Anthony C. Beilenson before the United Nations Association of the United States of America. 1994 Jun 10. 22 l. Typescript (large type, photocopy)
    - Family planning: ACB statement. f.8 of 9 (Box 262, Folder 8)
      Statement of Hon. Anthony C. Beilenson in support of an amendment to increase funding for international population stabilization. No date. 17 l. Typescript (large type, photocopy)
    - Family planning: ACB statement. f.9 of 9 (Box 262, Folder 9)
      Summary statement. 4 l. Typescript (large type, photocopy)
    - Population: Europe (Box 262, Folder 10)
    - Population: Latin America. f.1 of 2 (Box 262, Folder 11)
    - Population: Latin America. f.1 of 2 (Box 262, Folder 12)
    - Population: Middle East. f.1 of 2 (Box 262, Folder 13)
    - Population: Middle East. f.2 of 2 (Box 262, Folder 14)
    - Population: ACB speech (Box 262, Folder 15)
      Politics and Society: Political Challenges of Confronting Population Growth. ca. 1995. 9 l. Typescript (printer). With this: correspondence with UCLA editor of volume in which it is to appear, manuscript version printed in larger type and version with suggested corrections
    - Population: Africa. f.1 of 2 (Box 262, Folder 16)
    - Population: Africa. f.2 of 2 (Box 262, Folder 17)
    - Population: Asia. f.1 of 2 (Box 262, Folder 18)
    - Population: Asia. f.2 of 2 (Box 262, Folder 19)
      Clippings (newsprints)
    - International Conference on Population and Development - preparatory (Box 262, Folder 20)
      Proposals, pre conference items. An extensive file
    - Population, teenage pregnancy, etc (Box 262, Folder 21)
    - Base closings (Box 263, Folder 1)
    - Defense budgets (Box 263, Folder 2)
    - Arms sales / transfers (Box 263, Folder 3)
    - Defense restructuring (Bottom up review) (Box 263, Folder 4)
      Reports, including that from Secretary of Defense
    - Defense budget, base closings - relation to California (Box 263, Folder 5)
      Reports. Includes letter from Governor Pete Wilson, 1993 Apr 22
    - Arms: legislation (Box 263, Folder 6)
      CRS report, Defense Budget Project report
    - Arms: U.S. policy. f.1 of 2 (Box 264, Folder 1)
    - Arms: U.S. policy. f.2 of 2 (Box 264, Folder 2)
    - Arms: control (Box 264, Folder 3)
    - Arms: country cases (Box 264, Folder 4)
    - Arms: Iraq (Box 264, Folder 5)
    - Arms: proposals (Box 264, Folder 6)
    - Arms: ACB on ending arms sales. f.1 of 2 (Box 264, Folder 7)
      Clipping, draft from staff
    - Arms: ACB on ending arms sales. f.2 of 2 (Box 264, Folder 8)
      Articles, in various formats, as letters to the editor of the New York Times, the Los Angeles Times, and Monitor version. Each has separate title
    - Arms: U.S. data (Box 264, Folder 9)
      Reports, statistics, clippings
    - Arms: data and description (Box 264, Folder 10)
      Reports, clippings. An extensive file
    - Defense conversion task force (Box 264, Folder 11)
      Roster
    - Defense budget (Box 264, Folder 12)
      Statements from ACB, clippings
    - Defense budget (Box 264, Folder 13)
      Statements from ACB, analyses, clippings
    - Defense budget (Box 264, Folder 14)
      Reports, analyses, clippings
    - Defense conversion. f.1 of 4 (Box 265, Folder 1)
      Letters from President Bill Clinton, enclosing reports. 1993 Apr 1, 1995 Feb 9
    - Defense conversion. f.2 of 4 (Box 265, Folder 2)
    - Defense conversion. f.3 of 4 (Box 265, Folder 3)
    - Defense conversion. f.4 of 4 (Box 265, Folder 4)
    - Defense: environment (nuclear clean up) (Box 265, Folder 5)
      Statement, U.S. map
    - Defense budget (Box 265, Folder 6)
      DSG fact sheet, memos from chair, House Armed Services Committee
    - Defense op ed (Box 265, Folder 7)
      DSG fact sheet, draft from staff
    - California Steel Industries (Box 265, Folder 8)